There are surprisingly few shoe stores.
靴屋さんって意外にないね
Hey, not much.
ねえ、あんまりないですよ
Around here, like this.
この辺とか、こうやって
Something like sandals.
サンダルっぽいやつ
This is fine.
これで大丈夫
good?
いい?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Girls, you love these pajamas.
女の子、このパジャマ好きだよね
I have it.
持ってる
Do you have it?
持ってる?
I'd love to see you in pajamas like that.
そういうパジャマ姿見てみたいね
In pajamas?
パジャマ姿?
So, should we sleep over sometime?
じゃあいつかお泊りしたらいいですか?
Just get out of bed.
ちょっとベッド出して
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
My heart is pounding.
ドキドキする
What's this invisibility?
なにこのスケスケの?
cute.
かわいい
After all, it might feel better to hug each other naked.
やっぱ、裸と裸で抱き合った方が気持ちいいかも
This is also separate.
これはまた、これが別々だ
Please take a look.
見てください
What did you just check?
今何チェックしたの?
Did you check anything just now?
今何かチェックしたの?
I don't know.
知ってない
Don't you know?
知ってない?
I don't know.
知ってない
What did you check?
何チェックしたの?
Is there a timer?
タイマーあるかな?
Or like this.
とかこうやって
Did you check it?
チェックした?
I checked.
チェックした
Don't worry, this plastic is very Daniel.
大丈夫、これプラとってもダニエルあるから
It disappears.
無くなる
Will it disappear?
無くなる?
I feel like it never went away.
無くななかった気がする
I just bought it.
買ったばっかり
Did you buy it?
買 った?
Want to eat today?
今日は食べに?
Are you going to eat today's date?
今日のデートは食べに?
be.
ある
be?
ある?
There is.
あるよ
This hand is in the way.
これ手が邪魔だな
This hand gets in the way.
これ手が邪魔する
Toku Toku?
トクトクする?
This feels good too.
こっちも気持ちいい
I want to get in touch with you here.
ここに接し飛ばしたい
This is kind of hectic, isn't it?
これ なんかヘッチだよね
Are you wearing a T-bag today too?
今日もTバッグなの?
T-bag today too.
今日もTバッグ
Have you ever used toys?
おもちゃとか使ったことある?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
like?
好き?
toys.
おもちゃ
like.
好き
Do you like it?
好きなの?
When I was taking a bath earlier, I discovered something.
さっきお風呂入ってた時に、 何か発見しちゃったんだよね
Have you discovered it?
発見しちゃった?
You haven't discovered it, have you?
発見してないでしょ
Haven't you noticed?
気づいてない?
I haven't noticed.
気づいてない
You haven't noticed, have you?
気づいてないでしょ
Can I bring you some?
ちょっと持ってきていい?
It really happened.
本当にあったんだよ
This this.
これこれ
Try pulling it out a little.
ちょっと抜いてみて
I was really pissed.
ガチになったよ
I became serious.
ガチになった
Look, there's proper etiquette.
ほら、ちゃんとエチケットゴムある
This isn't a neckline anymore.
これはもうネックルじゃないよね
Can you take this off?
これ外してくれる?
The power was on.
電源入ってたよ
Should I wear this etiquette rubber?
これエチケットゴムつける?
Is it above?
上かな?
I'll put this here.
これ、ここにつけるでしょ
I'm going to put it on here and keep it hygienic.
ここにつけて、衛生でいきます
This is really thick.
すごい分厚いね、これ
I can go.
い ける
difficult.
難しい
Can I go?
いけるかな?
difficult.
難しい
Don't need it?
いらない?
Is it okay without it?
無くていいか?
Can I guess?
当てていいの?
I became serious.
ガチになった
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
The momentum is.
勢いは
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
Tell me.
言ってね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Let's stand in a straight line.
直線立てよう
My pants are moving.
パンツ動いちゃうもんね
Is it moving?
動いてるかな?
Are your pants moving?
パンツ動いてる?
Ah, it's beautiful.
あ、綺麗だ
Are you wet?
濡 れてる?
Oh, it's wet.
あ、濡れてる
It's really wet.
ちゃんと濡れてますよ
Tell me it hurt.
痛かったって言ってよ
Can I go as many times as I want?
何回でもいけるの?
Not yet?
まだいけない?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
amazing.
すごい
I'll try to use it again later.
後でまた使おうと
If I get a phone call first, wouldn't it be enough if I told you something?
最初に電話があったら、 くにとかしたら物足りないかな?
yes?
そう?
Shall I lick it?
舐めようか?
different.
違う
Lick it?
舐めたげ?
Air course?
エアコース?
Do you like being teased?
くにされるの好き?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
happy.
嬉しい
Thank you for doing so much.
いっぱいやってくれて
What are you eating now?
何食わえてるの今?
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくない?
calm down.
落ち着いて
Do you like doing things like licking?
ペラとかするの好きなの?
I don't hate it.
嫌いじゃない
dislike?
嫌い?
What if I say I hate you now?
今、嫌いって言ったら?
Don't you hate it?
嫌いじゃないの?
Do you feel like saying something if you don't like it?
嫌いしたら言いたくなったりする?
Is there one?
あるの?
If you want to say it, you can put it in the question.
言いたくなったら質問に入れていいよ
Then I want to put it in.
じゃあ入れたい
Did you get in?
入 れた?
That's amazing, outside.
すごいね、外
You can see everything through these sleeves.
丸見えるよ、この袖
I can see everything.
いろいろ丸見える
Now, this is all you have.
さあ、これしかない
This is it, then.
これなんだ、じゃあ
Touch it.
触って
Put your feet down.
足を置いて
copper?
どう?
Touch it.
触って
touch?
触る?
Become water.
お水になって
No, me.
いや、私
It was there, wasn't it?
あったよね
I hate seeing people complain.
文句見るの嫌いだよ
What is this?
これ何?
Because it's gone up.
あがってんだからね
Enough?
もういい?
Make it thinner.
もっと細くして
How do you like it?
いかが?
delicious?
おいしい?
it hurts?
痛い?
Are you together?
一緒なの?
why?
なんで?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Let's go.
いけよ
What about it?
い かが?
it hurts.
痛い
pain
痛
Is it?
い の?
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
痛 いの?
it hurts.
痛 い
Does it hurt?
痛 いの?
it hurts.
痛 い